{ "results": [
    {
        "category": "Science: Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "How many kilobytes in one gigabyte (in decimal)?",
        "correct_answer": "1000000",
        "incorrect_answers": [
        "1024",
        "1000",
        "1048576"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is it called when you stop an api request in a testing environment?",
        "correct_answer": "intercepting",
        "incorrect_answers": [
        "fumbling",
        "scrimmage",
        "blocking"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the bit of (possibly fake) data provided to an intercept called?",
        "correct_answer": "stub",
        "incorrect_answers": [
        "decoy",
        "lie",
        "alias"
        ]
        },
        {
        "category": "Science: Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What type of server stores no data about its user's identity or activity?",
        "correct_answer": "stateless",
        "incorrect_answers": [
        "blank",
        "boring",
        "lazy"
        ]
        },
        {
        "category": "Science: Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What does CRUD stand for?",
        "correct_answer": "Change, Read, Update, Delete",
        "incorrect_answers": [
        "Cancel, Read, Understand, Delay",
        "Can't Really Understate Difficulty",
        "Cool Risks Undermine Determination"
        ]
        },
        {
        "category": "Science: Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is it called when you check to make sure you have the right data type?",
        "correct_answer": "Typechecking",
        "incorrect_answers": [
        "Being extra careful",
        "DataLooking",
        "TypeScript"
        ]
        },
        {
        "category": "Science: Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Which hook is most similar to componentDidMount?",
        "correct_answer": "useEffect",
        "incorrect_answers": [
        "useRef",
        "useHistory",
        "useState"
        ]
        },
        {
        "category": "Science: Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Which hook doesn't cause a re-render?",
        "correct_answer": "useRef",
        "incorrect_answers": [
        "none - they all do",
        "useHistory",
        "useState"
        ]
        },
        {
        "category": "Science: Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Which best describes the flow of data in React?",
        "correct_answer": "Data down, actions up",
        "incorrect_answers": [
        "Actions down, data up",
        "Inheritance from ancestors",
        "Sibling to sibling"
        ]
        },
        {
        "category": "Science: Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is Alycia's favorite reality TV show?",
        "correct_answer": "Great British Baking Show",
        "incorrect_answers": [
        "The Bachelor",
        "Floor is Lava",
        "Drag Race"
        ]
        }
]
}